<!-- <resources>
    <string name="app_name">KidsBox</string>
 -->




<resources>

    <!-- App Title -->
    <string name="app_name">KidsBox - Fun Learning Games</string>

    <!-- Tagline (Appears under app name on Play Store) -->
    <string name="app_tagline">Play, Learn &amp; Grow — Math, Memory, Colors &amp; Puzzles for Kids</string>

    <!-- Long Description (SEO + ASO optimized for 2025 global ranking) -->
    <string name="app_description">
        KidsBox is the ultimate fun learning app for children, students, and families worldwide .
        Designed for playful education, it helps kids learn through exciting math puzzles,
        memory games, color tap challenges, and real money counter practice (INR &amp; USD).

         Learn Addition, Subtraction, Multiplication &amp; Division in a joyful, game-based way.
         Boost focus, logic, memory, and problem-solving skills through engaging mini-games.
         Explore color tap &amp; matching challenges for brain stimulation and visual learning.
         Learn money counting with real-world currencies — Indian Rupees (₹) and US Dollars ($).
         Solve math puzzles, mazes, and number challenges — perfect for preschoolers to grown-ups.

        KidsBox is 100% safe, offline-ready, and ad-free, built especially for kids aged 3+ to 12.
        Parents love it. Teachers recommend it. Kids enjoy it every day!

         FEATURES
        Educational games for math, memory, and color learning
         Offline support — no internet needed after setup
         Ad-free mode — safe and family-friendly
         Multi-age learning for toddlers, preschoolers, and students
         Simple interface — easy to play, hard to put down!

         Ideal for India, USA, UK, Canada, Australia, Japan &amp; global users
         Turn screen time into smart learning time — download KidsBox today!
    </string>

    <!-- Keyword Bank (used for internal reference and SEO planning) -->
    <string name="app_keywords">
        kids learning games, fun learning app, educational games for kids, math puzzles,
        memory match, color games, preschool learning, math learning app, counting money,
        INR USD money counter, brain training for kids, fun math for kids,
        puzzle games for children, offline educational app, safe learning app,
        kidsbox math learning, toddler learning app, free kids games,
        family educational app, color tap challenge, play and learn game,
        global kids education app, best math app for kids, interactive learning game,
        kids brain games, preschool education app, kindergarten math, logical thinking, iq games for kids, kids brain games, preschool education app, kindergarten math, logical thinking, iq games for kids

    </string>

    <!-- Locale and Category Metadata -->
    <string name="app_locale">en, hi, ja</string>
    <string name="app_category">Education, Kids, Family, Puzzle, Learning, Brain Training</string>

    <!-- Regional Targeting -->
    <string name="app_region_target">India, USA, UK, Canada, Australia, Japan, Europe</string>

    <!-- Age Group and Audience -->
    <string name="app_target_age">3+, preschool, students, parents, teachers</string>

    <!-- Author Metadata -->
    <string name="app_author">Ashish Kumar</string>

    <!-- Promotional Line (for Play Console Promo Text section) -->
    <string name="app_promo">✨ Play, Learn &amp; Grow — Fun math &amp; memory games loved by kids &amp; parents worldwide!</string>
    <string name="app_keywords_hi">बच्चों का लर्निंग गेम, गणित खेल, रंग सीखने का ऐप, पहेली गेम</string>
    <string name="app_keywords_ja">子供向け学習ゲーム, 数学パズル, カラーマッチ, メモリーゲーム</string>


</resources>
